Lee, um I read somewhere that uh you
used your NIL money for a pretty cool
cause. Um can you can you explain uh why
it was important to you? I I read it
right that you used your NIL money to
get your mom a house, right?
>> Yes. Yes, sir.
>> Uh why was that important to you?
>> Uh no, you know, uh God bless I really
use that saying God bless you to bless
others. So when when I when I got that
bliss and first person I thought about
was my mom and my and my um baby girls.
>> Yeah, absolutely. All right, thanks man.
>> All right, we'll go with Kathy Hill
followed by Scott Fowler.
>> Hey Lee, how's it going?
>> Good. How you doing?
>> Good. As a fellow Mobile native, happy
to have you here with us now.
>> No, so glad to be there.
>> Um sorry if you've already been asked
this. just got on. But I heard that
Derek Brown is a pretty big idol of
yours. Uh what do you like about
watching him play and have you been able
to talk to him recently as you've kind
of gone through this process?
>> Oh yeah, I just talked to Derek like uh
like five like 10 minutes ago. He told
me just just be ready to work and and
come on, let's let's get it. But just
seeing his game, how how violent he is,
how he put hands on people, and how he
uh chased down tackles outside the
tackle box, how most majority of his
plays come behind in the back field and
behind the outside tackle box.
>> And then again, sorry if you've already
been asked this, but where did your
nickname the fridge originate from?
>> Uh my my nickname, the fridge, it was
originated from my defense coordinator
gave it in high school and I he said,
"I'm sorry, I call you fridge." I said,
"Why coach?" He said, "If people want to
eat, they got to get to you." So, I took
that and ran with it.
>> It works. Thank you so much.
>> Uh, hey Lee, Scott Fowler from the
Charlotte Observer, uh, the local paper
here. Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> Um, I wanted to ask you one two things.
One was also about the fridge, but So,
did did that follow you all through your
college stops? And do you embrace that
nickname? You want Panther fans to call
you that?
>> Yeah, I embraced it. I embraced it.
Follow me. and our love for the Pers
fridge.
>> Okay. And uh for those who have never
seen you play before, can you describe
your style of play?
>> Someone who violent. She going to draw
seeing me put hands on on the big guys
on offensive line and someone who bring
energy to the team and to the crawl and
you go in the drawer. Watch Carolina's
football play.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, we'll go with Joe Pson
followed by Mike Lette.
Hey Lee, congrats man. I'm with the
Athletic here. How you doing?
>> Good, thank you.
>> Yeah, man. Where where are you calling
in from?
>> I'm calling in from Atlanta.
>> What's going on in Atlanta?
>> Uh, no, just me and my family. We had a
big day down here. Really just enjoying
the moment with them.
>> Nice. You uh you grew up in Mobile, but
y'all your folks live in Atlanta now. Is
that right?
>> I grew up Mobile, but we just had the
draft party in Mobile.
>> Got it. Got it. Hey, uh, wanted to ask
you, uh, how did you first become a a
fan of Derek Brown? Uh,
>> Auburn, watching Auburn football play
growing up. And as I got close to
commit, I was just watching Auburn. Uh,
Coach G, I always talk to him, showing
me feel about him. So, uh, I seen this
tape, see these play, seeing how he how
he do play his game, and I just enjoy
enjoying play.
>> You didn't have a long stay at Auburn.
take us through uh that part of your
your journey.
>> Uh my journey at Auburn uh it was pretty
fun. Uh laidback, relaxing. Uh was glad
to be our Tiger. Uh just made a decision
to leave that place based off my family
and my situation.
>> Out of your your moves you made, which
one you think was the most uh impactful
and uh you know helped you get to where
you are tonight?
uh when Texas Tech really helped me uh
get better as a player. Uh UCF helped me
and allowed me to uh get get better as a
as a personal human being and the player
I grow, but Texas Tech was just one of
the main schools that just helped me
just grow in many ways and show my craft
more on the football side of it.
>> Thanks Lee. Thank you.
>> Hi Lee Michael from uh Carolina Sports
Live. How quickly did everything sort of
come together for you tonight? I mean, I
know with the Panthers moving up, that
caught us by surprise at that point. Did
you start realizing things were moving
or did this whole thing catch you by
surprise?
>> It caught me by No, that's how I was
expecting it uh to go whichever type
way, but uh I'm blessed and just glad to
have the opportunity to be a panther
now.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, we have time for a couple
more. We'll go with Mike Kay followed by
Bash Tyurt.
>> Hey Lee, congratulations and welcome.
This is a a bit of a hybrid defense, but
it's traditionally a three four front.
What do you like about the job of a nose
tackle or at least playing in an odd
front? And how important is it to you to
open up, you know, pass rushing lanes
for your teammates? Oh, just just being
Lee Hunter all the time. Trusting my uh
preparation, my craft that I I didn't
worked on and all my life and all my
career and just just learn from guys
around me that's been there done that
for a long time now and and just get
better and just be violent and put hands
on people and help the Pelters reach the
best stage they could.
>> Have you gotten to meet with Todd Wash?
Uh do you know anything about him? Um
he's a pretty outgoing I would say sort
of coach. I just didn't know if you had
any background with him.
>> Yeah, I communicate with him. Pretty
chill guy, laidback guy, a little ball
and uh from what from my understanding.
So I'm just excited to be a pen now and
uh just such a bliss.
>> Congrats.
>> Thank you.
>> Hi Lee Vashtard with Carolina Blitz.
Welcome to Carolina. Um, I I I see that
you're number two, and I know that guys
are are they're particular about their
numbers. How did you get number two?
I've never seen a defensive lineman with
the number two.
>> I was seven in high school, but I
couldn't get seven. I I couldn't get two
at UCF. So, I was like, I was blowing
July 2nd, 2002, so I may well rock for
numbers two is open. So, when I seen
them two open, I thought about that. I
took it and ran with it. And it looked
very well on me. Right.
Are you gonna try to carry that into the
league?
>> Uh, I would love to, but whatever them I
get, I'm grateful.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> We'll end with Mike Salerte.
>> Thanks, Kia. Congratulations, Lee. Uh,
the fact that Carolina thought so highly
of you to move up two spots to draft
you, what does that say to a player and
what kind of a message do you get from
that that they said this is our guy, we
got to go get him? What what type of
message I get from it is they traded up
two spots. They wanted me. They came and
got me. They show love and interest. So,
what response they gonna get from me?
I'm ready to run through brick wall for
them.
>> We can fix that. We can fix that in
post. Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, Lee. Thank you so much for
taking the time join us and once again,
congratulations.
>> Thank you.
Nat.